You're telling me
this actress person...
...is the only woman you ever wanted
who didn't want you back?
Oh, my God.
Is this what it's like to be you?
-You're crazy about her, huh?
-You have no idea.
When we're on stage, I get to
kiss her and touch her.
She goes home with the director...
...and it's like somebody's
ripping out my heart.
Oh, it's so great to see you
feeling like this.
Dad called this morning.
Aunt Sylvia passed away.
We were all
pretty shaken up about it.
Am I missing something?
I thought death was supposed
to be sad, in a way.
Well, Aunt Sylvia was...
... not a nice person.
She was a cruel, cranky old bitch.
And I'm sorry she died.
Did Dad say I get the dollhouse?
-You get the dollhouse.
-I get the dollhouse!
A house for dolls!
That is so cool.
When I was a kid, I had a barrel.
You had a barrel for a dollhouse?
No, just a barrel.
You know what? You can play
with my dollhouse.
Really?
Any time you want.
When I was young I wanted
to play with this dollhouse.
But no! It was to be looked at,
never played with.
My grandmother said
the same thing to me.
The One With the Doll House
Thanks for lunch.
You didn't have to walk me here.
That's okay. No problem.
You realize we don't keep
the women's lingerie here.
Yes, I realize that.
-Summer catalog.
-That's the stuff.
Rachel, I need the Versace invoice.
You don't work for me.
Joanna, this is my friend
Chandler Bing. Joanna.
Bing? That's a great name.
It's Gaelic for,
"Thy turkey's done."
-I'm gonna go. Nice meeting you.
-You too.
So what's wrong with him?
Nothing. He's just goofy like that.
I actually hardly notice it anymore.
I mean, is he married
or involved with anyone?
He's not married or involved
with anyone.
Actually, you know what?
Forget it.
-I'll ask him for you, if you want.
-Would you?
Or is it too sad and desperate,
like something Sophie would do?
-I am here.
-I know that.
Look at it!
Wallpaper's a little faded.
That's okay.
Carpet's a little loose.
Hardwood floors?!
-It's so beautiful!
-I know!
So I'm here, ready to play!
I brought a bunch of stuff
for the house, so check it out.
What's this?
That's a dog.
Every house should have a dog.
Not one that can pee on the roof.
Maybe it's so big because the house
was built on radioactive waste.
And is this in case the house sneezes?
No, that's the ghost for the attic.
-I don't want a ghost.
-Well, nobody wants a ghost.
But you've got one...
... because the house is sitting on
an ancient lndian burial ground.
Wait a minute. The house
was built on radioactive waste...
...and an ancient
lndian burial ground?
That would never happen.
Obviously you don't know much
about the U.S. government.
-I need to talk to you.
-Sure. What's up?
Oh, sorry. I meant Chandler.
I know.
Well, if something comes up....
I'm glad you guys are past
that little awkward phase.
My boss. Joanna. When you left...
...she started asking questions
about you....
Liked what she saw?
Dug my action, did she?
Checking out the Chan Chan Man!
That was...
...surreal.
What do you think?
Are you interested?
She seemed cool. Attractive.
I'll do it.
Thank you, Chandler.
This is great. She's gonna love me.
Dinosaur attack!
Quick, everybody into the house!
All right, Phoebe, you know what?
That's it. That's it.
No dinosaurs, no ghosts,
no giant dogs, okay?
They're not the right size, they're
not Victorian and they don't go.
Fine.
Come, dinosaur. We're not welcome
in the house of no imagination.
While we're on the subject,
I have to say that dinosaurs...
...they don't go, "ruff!"
The little ones do.
-Hey, Kate.
-Morning.
I went to that restaurant
you talked about
Hey, lovely.
Come, talk to me for a minute.
I ate the food. It was good.
I had the fish.
I'm Lauren. Kate's understudy.
Joey Tribbiani.
I know.
I'm a big fan of yours.
What?
I used to schedule my classes
so I could watch Dr. Drake Ramoray...
...on Days of our Lives.
-Get out of here. Really?
-Absolutely.
But then they dropped you
down that elevator shaft.
They gave me the shaft, all right.
You're so funny.
What are you doing after rehearsal?
You want to get a drink?
Sure. A drink sounds great.
-Cool. I'll see you then.
-All right.
All right. It's time to act,
my talking props.
Look everybody!
Look at my new dollhouse!
Look, look!
Hey, what's this?
It's a slide instead of stairs.
Look.
Very interesting, Phoebe.
What's this?
The licorice room.
You can eat all the furniture.
And when guests come over, they can
stay on the Tootsie Roll-away bed.
This is the coolest house ever!
Does anyone want to join me
in the Aroma Room?
-All right.
-I would.
Hey, guys? Guys!
Did you see my new china cabinet?
Watch. Watch.
And? And?
Hey, my father's house does that.
How did it go?
Tell me everything!
The movie was great...
...dinner was great, and there's nothing
like a cool, crisp New York evening.
Of course, I didn't enjoy any of that
because Joanna's such a dull dud!
Chandler is fantastic!
-What?
-You know how people just click?
He came by to pick me up, I opened
the door and it was just like, "click!"
Did he tell you?
Doesn't he have a good heart?
And he's so sweet. He said he'd
call, so put him straight through.
-lsn't this great?
-Don't spoil it.
Come on, baby, don't go. Please?
What do you say?
It's you.
Just one sec.
I'm going to take this call.
When I continue,
I hope there will appear on-stage...
...this magical thing
that in the theater we call...
...committing to the moment!
The guy's like a cartoon.
What do you see in him, anyway?
He happens to be brilliant.
Which is more than I can say
for that sweater you're dating.
I'm not interested in her sweater.
It's what's underneath her sweater
that counts.
And besides...
...since when do you care
who I'm with?
I don't care.
Why, do you want me to care?
Do you want me to want you to care?
Do you?
What?
Okay. I'm afraid to say this,
but let's pick up where we left off.
Come on, baby, don't go. Please?
What do you say?
I've got no reason to stay.
Stop!
Stop it! You must stop!
You are bad actors!
This is a terrible play!
I'll see you in the morning.
I can't believe we go on
in a week.
Hey, it's gonna be all right.
Since we're getting off early,
do you want to go paint mugs?
What?
At the place I told you about
last night?
Yeah, with the mug-painting.
I was so listening to that.
But you know what?
I need to work on my stuff tonight.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Are you okay?
I guess.
What are we gonna do about the scene?
I don't know.
Maybe if it had more heat.
Well, how do you mean?
Adrianne's looking for a reason
to stay, right?
Victor can't just kiss her.
He's gotta...
... he's gotta give her a reason.
Maybe he could slip her the tongue.
Or maybe...
... maybe he could grab her
and lift her up.
Then Adrianne could wrap her legs
around his waist.
Then she could rip off his shirt and
kiss his chest and stomach.
Then he could use his teeth
to undo her dress and...
...and bite her!
Then right when the scene ends,
he could take her...
...with this raw, animal....
Something like that?
That's pretty much
what I had in mind.
It's a little early to be drinking.
Things finally happened with Kate.
You're kidding? That's great.
It was so amazing.
After the lovemaking...
Oh, my.
... I just watched her sleep for hours.
Just breathing in...
...and breathing out.
I knew she was dreaming because...
... her eyes kept going like this.
I'm telling you,
she's got it all wrong.
All I said was, "This was fun.
Let's do it again sometime.
I'll give you a call."
I wonder why she thinks you're going
to call her?
It's what you say at the end
of a date.
You can't just say,
"Nice to meet you. Good night?"
To her face?
I'm standing there...
...she's waiting for me to say
I'll call her...
...and it comes out.
I can't help it.
It's a compulsion.
When a guy says he'll call,
it doesn't mean he's going to call.
This never happened to you?
Well, they always called.
Bite me.
-Did he call?
-No, sorry.
Why? He said he'd call.
Why hasn't he called?
Maybe he's intimidated by smart,
strong, successful women.
Sophie, will you please
climb out of my butt.
Why hasn't he called, Rachel? Why?
Maybe he feels awkward because
you're my boss.
Awkward? Why should he feel awkward?
You didn't tell him
not to call me, did you?
If you're uncomfortable with
your friend dating me...
...there are always ways to fix that.
Call her. Call her now!
Multiple so many paper cuts.
"Why hasn't he called, Rachel?
Why, why? I don't understand!"
I'm telling you, she's flipped out!
She's gone crazy!
Well, give me the phone then.
She thinks it's my fault
you haven't called her.
You have to call her.
You can't call somebody
after this long to say:
"In case you didn't notice,
I don't like you."
Then you'll have to
take her out again.
She's really dull,
and she gets this...
...gross mascara-goop thing
in the corner of her eye!
I don't care!
You'll take her out again
and end it...
...in a way she knows it's ended.
I don't care how hard it is.
Don't tell her you'll call her again!
All right, fine!
But just lunch.
From now on, I get my own dates.
I don't want you setting me up again!
That's fine!
-That's just a lot of big talk.
-I know.
I'm in the shower!
Fire! There's a fire! Fire!
I talked to Lauren.
I told her how things were with us.
Did you talk to Marshall?
About what?
About what happened with us.
No, there's really no reason
why he should find out.
So let's not make a big deal
out of it, okay?
What are you talking about?
It was a big deal.
You can't tell me last night
didn't mean something to you.
I was there.
You're not that good an actress.
I was just caught up in the moment.
That's all it was.
Joey, I'm sorry you feel bad, but...
... haven't you slept with a woman
and it meant more to her than to you?
Hi, pig!
Sorry I scared you in there.
It's okay.
By the way...
... I was just checking
the shower massager.
I tried to reach you at work.
There's been a fire.
What?
Oh, my God!
What happened?
We believe it originated here...
...in the Aroma Room.
Did everyone get out okay?
The giraffe's okay,
and so is the pirate.
-What's this?
-No, don't look!
You don't want to see
what's under there!
The foster puppets!
It's not a big deal. It's right
here, and it's all the time.
Thanks again for lunch.
-This was pleasant.
-lt was, wasn't it?
-The food there was great.
-Wasn't it?
So take care.
You too.
I'll give you a call.
We should do it again!
Great. I'm looking forward to it.
-Any messages?
-Sophie's desk.
Are you gonna call her?
I'm sorry, okay? I'm weak
and pathetic and sorry.
You are gonna tell her.
You'll tell her now.
I'm not gonna call you.
What?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I said I was going to
when I'm not.
This has nothing to do with you.
And this isn't Rachel's fault.
It's me.
I have serious problems
when it comes to women.
I have issues with commitment,
intimacy...
... mascara goop.
I'm really sorry. It's just that...
...this isn't going to work out.
This isn't how I was hoping
this would end...
... but I guess I have to appreciate
your honesty.
I'll give you a call.
We should do it again sometime!
Anyway, Beth,
what I'm saying is...
... I should have considered your
feelings before I went home with you.
I've recently learned what it's like
to be on your side...
...and I'm sorry.
Do you think you can forgive me?
Great. Thanks.
Hello, Jennifer?
Hi, Mrs. Laurio.
Is Jennifer there?
She's not home, huh?
Actually I kind of need
to talk to you too.